"The Last Oath"
(Episode 12: Casia)
Hang in there.
I'll get you somewhere
safe to treat that wound.
I'm fine.
Put me down.
I can walk.
You're still acting tough.
If you fall again,
I'll just have to carry you anyway.
The arrow was poisoned.
The poisoned blood is finally cleared out.
You...
Jerk.
Meeting you was a curse.
Get well soon.
The fever finally broke.
Leave me alone.
Go.
It's yours now.
Protect yourself.
I'm going with you,
but that doesn't make me your prisoner.
Getting to headquarters as soon as possible
is best for everyone.
Don't forget,
he's a hunter.
You're just his prey.
A lab rat he needs to catch.
Test if the target is immune.
Target confirmed as immune.
Taming a biting dog is simple.
Just pull out its fangs.
You bastard.
And to think I considered you a
friend and trusted you so much.
I just need to make sure you stay alive.
Let go, you jerk!
Don't force me to use
the same methods on you
that I use on everyone else.
Just go.
If you stay any longer,
you won't be able to leave.
Now is your best chance.
Lin Zai!
Don't leave me behind!
No, no!
Mom, Dad!
Useless trash.
If you can't get up on your own,
then rot here
and wait to die.
Don't go.
Don't leave me behind.
Why did you come back?
You could have left.
Even if you had abandoned me today,
I wouldn't have been surprised.
I'm used to it.
Used to what?
Used to being abandoned.
To save one's own life
by sacrificing others...
Isn't that human instinct?
When it really counts,
even your own parents
or comrades who have
been through hell with you
can't be relied on.
So you...
why did you come back?
A-Leh,
I'm not like them.
I have a heart.
S-So...
Listen, A-Leh.
If I go with you,
will I die?
I will risk my life
to protect you.
Is this OK?